Guide to the Frank Irvine papers, 1907-1939.
Irvine, Frank papers, 1907-1939
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Frank Irvine papers, 1907-1939.
18-1-463
Frank Irvine, 1858-1931.
.4 cubic ft.
Correspondence, minutes, speeches, and other material.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes correspondence pertaining to a course on patent law at Cornell, 1907-1908; correpondence between Irvine and other law school administrators in New York State, primarily concerning the New York Association of Law Instructors and its interest in the examination for and admission to the New York State Bar; minutes of a meeting of the association; and copies of speeches and other printed material.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Dean of the faculty, Cornell Law School.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes correspondence pertaining to a course on patent law at Cornell, 1907-1908; correpondence between Irvine and other law school administrators in New York State, primarily concerning the New York Association of Law Instructors and its interest in the examination for and admission to the New York State Bar; minutes of a meeting of the association; and copies of speeches and other printed material.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Irvine, Frank, 1858-1931.; Cornell Law School.; New York Association of Law Instructors.; New York State Bar Association.
Subjects:
Bar associations.; Law--Study and teaching.; College teachers.; Lawyers.
Form and Genre Terms:
Speeches.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Correspondence: Judge Frank Irvine - letters sent by Irvine, Sept. 1907-Nov. 1908 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Letters received by Irvine and some printed materials on Patent Law, Sept. 1907-Nov. 1908 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, Mar.-Dec. 1911 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, Jan.-Apr. 1912 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, May-Aug. 1912 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Correspondence, Sept.-Dec. 1912 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, Jan.-Mar. 1913 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Correspondence, Apr.-May 1913 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Correspondence, Aug.-Dec. 1913, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Lawyers' Institute, Aug. 1939 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Lawyers' Institute, Aug. 1939 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Miscellaneous, 1911-1931, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 12)